(忆往昔)
-你是谁  -卡西迪奥
- Who are you? - Castiel.
你究竟是什么
I mean what are you?
我是侍主的天使
I'm an angel of the lord.
你真是天使
Some angel you are.
我的真身
My true form
不是常人可以承受的
It can be overwhelming to humans
我的真声也一样无法承受
And so can my real voice...
当然你已经体味过了
But you already knew that.
只有少数人  少数特别之人
Certain people -- special people --
可以感知我的真容
Can perceive my true visage.
那你现在容貌又是什么
What visage are you in now, huh?
这个  这只是具皮囊罢了
This? this is...a vessel.
你侵占了某个可怜虫的身体
You're possessing some poor bastard?
他是名虔诚之徒
He's a devout man.
这正是他虔诚祈祷之愿
he actually prayed for this.
我在下面那段时间一定有事儿发生
Something major must have happened while I was downstairs,
因为我无力回天你就
'cause I can't back and --
你就和恶魔好上了
And you're bff with a demon?
为什么你如此信任她
Why do you trust her so much?
因为  她救过我的命
Because... she saved my life.
吸血  你自己也清楚那不对
Sucking blood? you got to know that's wrong.
我也祈求上天能让我停下来
I wish to god I could stop.
(如今)
我们得聊聊
We need to talk.
我这是在做梦  对吗
I'm dreaming, aren't I?
这儿不安全
It's not safe here.
需要更隐蔽的地方才行
Someplace more private.
更隐蔽  这会儿应该是意识交流吧
More private? we're inside my head.
没错
Exactly.
但会被某人偷听到
Someone could be listening.
卡西  出什么事儿了
Cass, what's wrong?
到这儿来见我
Meet me here.
马上  出发
Go -- now.
他到底要说什么  迪恩
What'd he say, Dean?
为什么需要如此谨慎
What was so important?
我要知道了  还需要来这儿吗
If I knew, would I be here?
搞什么鬼来着
What the hell?
就像个爆炸后的现场
Looks like a bomb went off.
这儿发生过打斗
There was a fight here.
双方都是什么人
Between who?
回头看看
Check it out.
觉得眼熟吗
Look familiar?
当然  见到过
Yeah, it does.
安娜曾用过相似的图形
Anna used something like that
将天使震飞
To wish the angels back to the cornfield.
那么  就是说  卡西在跟天使肉搏得吗
So, what? Cass was fighting angels?
不清楚
I don't know.
萨姆
Sam.
卡西
Cass?
Cass!
嘿  醒醒  卡西
Hey! Cass!
干嘛  出什么事儿了
What's -- what's going on?
别紧张  先放松点儿
Just take it easy. take it easy.
卡西  你没事儿吧
Cass, you okay?
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
我不是卡西迪奥
I'm not Castiel.
而是我
It's me.
这个我是指谁
Who's "me"?
吉米啊
Jimmy.
我的名字是吉米
My name's Jimmy.
该死的  那卡西迪奥去哪儿了
Where the hell is Castiel?
他不见了
He's gone.
慢点儿吃
Mind slowing down?
我真怕你噎着了
You're gonna give me angina.
我饿死了
I'm hungry.
你最后一次吃东西是什么时候
When's the last time you ate?
不记得了  数月前了吧
I don't know -- months.
究竟发生了什么事儿
What the hell happened back there?
那儿看起来像是天使大战之地
It looked like an angel battle royal.
我只记得一阵强光闪过  之后我
All I remember is there was a flash of light, and I, uh...
我  就醒了过来  而且恢复了自己的意识
I-I woke up, and I was just, you know, like, me again.
就是说  卡西已经离开了你的肉体
So, what -- Cass just ditched out of your meat suit?
我真不清楚了
I really don't know.
你记得自己被附身这段时间的事儿
You remember anything about being possessed?
所有的事儿都记得
Anything at all?
当然  所有细节都记得
Yeah, bits and pieces.
天使进驻你体内
I mean, angel inside of you --
就像是和一颗彗星绑在一起一般
It's kind of like being chained to a comet.
那听起来真不舒服
Well, that doesn't sound like much fun.
那还只是概述
Understatement.
卡西说有事儿要告诉我们
Cass said he wanted to tell us something.
拜托你还记得是什么事儿
Please tell me you remember that.
抱歉了
Sorry.
好吧  那你还知道些什么
Come on. what do you know?
知道我自己名叫吉米·诺瓦克
My name is Jimmy Novak.
来自伊利诺伊州的庞蒂亚克
I'm from Pontiac, Illinois.
有一个温馨之家
And I have a family.
庞蒂亚克   伊利诺伊州
一年前
克莱尔
Claire.
感谢你赐予的食物  圣洁的主
Bless this food, o lord,
我们将无比珍惜你的赐予
And ourselves to thy loving service,
我们将一如既往地秉承对你信念和敬畏
That we may always continue in thy faith and fear
遵父之名为圣
To the honor and glory of thy name.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
我发现自己的头已经伸出
I can see my head sticking out
车子的前保险杠了
From underneath the front bumper.
我双眼被蒙着
My eyes were closed.
当我将头向右转时
My head was turned to the right side.
看到我两肩上都站着一个天使
And on each side of me is an angel, and, uh...
没信号了
blank
那我们该怎么做
So, what do we do?
什么意思  这家伙可是有家人的
What do you mean? the guy's got a family.
当然是给他买张车票  让他打道回府呗
We buy him a bus ticket, send him home.
我不同意这个做法
I don't know about that.
迪恩  他可是我们唯一的线索
Dean, he's the only lead we got.
但他一问三不知的
He doesn't know anything.
你真相信他不知道吗
Are you 100% about that?
你是说他在骗我们
You think he's lying?
那你打算把他关禁闭好好审他吗
Well, you want to go guantanamo on the guy?
迪恩  也许他潜意识里是清楚事实的
Dean, maybe he doesn't even know what he knows.
我觉得至少可以带他去鲍比那儿
I say at least we get him to Bobby's.
也许能让他试试  催眠或是通灵
Maybe all he needs is -- is hypnosis or a p-psychic,
说不定  只不过是在他体内沉睡了
Or, hell, maybe Cass will just drop back into him.
我不这么想  老弟
I don't know, man.
迪恩  想想看  那儿曾发生过天使之间争斗
Dean, back there, that was angel-on-angel violence.
虽然现在我不清楚究竟发生了什么
Now, I don't know what's going on,
但必定是大事
but it's big,
我们不能就这样错过手中唯一的线索
And we can't just let the only lead we've got just skip out.
怎么啦
What?
还记得我们帮助众人的目的吧
Remember when our job was helping people --
不就是让他们能重新团聚吗
Like getting them back to their family?
你觉得我不想帮他
You think I don't want to help him?
我只不过是就事论事
I'm just being realistic.
我也是在想办法帮他
I mean, hell, we're doing him a favor.
何以见得
How?!
迪恩  我们想从他这儿探出所以然
Dean, if we want to question the guy,
你觉得那些恶魔会不想吗
You can damn well bet the demons do, too.
你俩说什么呢  我不能回家啥意思
What the hell are you talking about, I can't go home?
因为你现在可是众矢之的
There's a good chance you have a bull's-eye on your back.
什么意思
What?
都是什么人来着
From who?
恶魔们
Demons.
得了吧  别瞎扯了
Oh, come on. that's crazy.
他们想要我干嘛
What do they want with me?
不好说  追问事实真相吧  也许
I don't know -- information, maybe.
我已经说了啥都不知道
I don't know anything!
我知道  不过
I know, but --
听着  我的任务已经完成了  明白吗
Look, I'm done, okay?
什么恶魔  天使的  都不关我事儿了
With demons, angels -- all of it.
我现在只想回家
I just want to go home.
我们明白
We understand.
不  我觉得你根本就不了解
No, I don't think that you do understand.
我被枪击过  被刀刺过再被救活
I've been shot and stabbed and healed,
我的躯体被别人使唤着满世界转悠
And my body's been dragged all over the earth.
虽被神选中了  但我已经完成使命了
By some miracle, I'm out, and I am done.
我付出得够多了  明白吗
I've given enough, okay?
听着  我们只是想告诉你
Look, all we're saying is that until we figure this out,
跟我们一起才是最安全的
The safest place is with us.
那要多久
How long?
至少得到我们搞清楚整件事为止
We'll cross that bridge when we get to it.
你要去哪
Where you going?
去看望我的妻子和女儿不行吗
To see my wife and daughter, okay?
不行
No, you're not.
你只会让他们身处险境
You're just gonna put those people in danger.
也就是说我现在成了囚犯
So, what -- now I'm a prisoner?
我们也不想的
Harsh way to put it.
迪恩
Dean!
你能不能麻利点
Would you hurry up?
很好笑吗
Sorry -- uh, this is funny to you?
大块头狱警
Mr. big bad prison guard,
吉米·麦克穆克 从你眼皮底下溜走了
And Jimmy Mcmook gives you the slip?
的确很好笑
Yeah, it's pretty funny.
你那时在干吗
What were you doing, anyway?
我去买可乐
I was getting a coke.
是不是提神的可乐
Was it a refreshing coke?
可以走了吗
Can we just go, please?
-你到底在搞什么  -没事  我没事
- What the hell are you doing?! - It's okay. I'm okay.
吉米
Jimmy.
你看
Look.
-你怎么了  -我没事
- What's wrong with you? - Nothing's wrong.
他叫我这么做的
He asked me to do it.
谁叫你做的
Who asked you to do it?
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
来表明我的信仰
To prove my faith.
你看
Look.
我没事
I'm fine.
真是奇迹啊
It's a miracle.
卡西迪奥是谁
Who's Castiel?
两位好啊
Hey, guys.
天哪
Geez!
开稳点
Smooth.
你就不会提前打声招呼吗
You ever try calling ahead?
我喜欢惊喜
I like the element of surprise.
你气色很好
You look terrific.
是的
Um...yeah.
迪恩  现在说这个不是很合适
Not the most appropriate time, Dean.
你们让吉米逃掉了
You let Jimmy get away?
跟当事人说吧
Talk to ginormo here.
萨姆
Sam...
你看起来有点不一样
You seem...different.
我不知道  我的新发型吗
Me? I don't know. Haircut?
我说的不是那个
That's not what I'm talking about.
吉米跟你说了什么  他还记得什么
So, what'd Jimmy tell you? he remember anything?
干嘛问这个  出什么事了
Why? what's going on?
卡西被送回去了
It's Cass. He got sent back home.
其实更像被拽回去的
Well, more like dragged back.
回天堂吗
To heaven?
不是好事吗
That's not a good thing?
不是  这是很糟糕的事
No. That's a very bad thing.
很痛苦  很糟糕
Painfully, awfully bad.
他一定把谁惹毛了
He must have seriously pissed someone off.
卡西说有重要事情跟我说
Cass said he had something to tell me, something important.
-什么事  -我不知道
- What? - I don't know.
吉米知道吗
Does Jimmy know?
我认为他不知道
I don't think so.
你认为
You don't think so?
不管什么事  肯定是大事
Whatever it is, it's huge.
你要查明真相
You got to find out for sure.
所以我们才去追吉米
That's why we're going after Jimmy.
所以你一开始就不应该让他逃了
That's why you shouldn't have let him go in the first place.
他可能已经死了
He's...probably dead already.
把药吃了
Take the pills.
我没病
I'm not sick.
吉米  把药吃了
Jimmy, take the pills.
我知道这很难理解
I know that this is hard to understand...
但他选择了我
But he chose me.
那个叫卡西迪奥的天使吗
Castiel the angel?
他跟我说过话  艾姆斯
He's spoken to me now, Ames
很多次了
A dozen times.
你相信上帝  对吧
Hey, you believe in god, don't you?
这算什么问题  我当然信
What kind of question is that? of course.
天使呢
And angels?
我也信  吉米
Yes, Jimmy.
那为什么  你就不肯相信
So, why is it, then, so hard for you to believe
他们跟我说话
That they're talking to me?
吉米  你是收音机广告销售员
Jimmy, you sell ad time for a.m. radio.
不对  他说我很特别  而且是与生俱来的
No, he said that I'm special, it's in my blood.
什么叫你与生俱来
W-what does that mean, it's in your blood? hmm?
他没说
He didn't say.
他只说上帝选择我做更重要的事情
He just said that god has chosen me for a higher purpose.
要做什么
To do what?
这是上帝的旨意
You know, it's god's will.
轮不到我回答
Not really my place to question it.
你过来
Hey, come here.
这是上帝的赐福
This is a blessing.
是我一生中最重要的事情
This is the most important thing to ever happen to me.
我以为对你来说
I thought we were the most important things
我们才是最重要的事情
To ever happen to you.
拥有信仰
Hey, have faith.
吉米  你吓到我了
Jimmy... you're scaring me.
上帝会赐予的
God will provide.
如果你不吃药  不寻求帮助
If you won't take your pills and if you won't get help...
我明早就带着克莱尔回娘家
...then I'm gonna take Claire to my mother's in the morning.
我愿意帮你
so, I want to help you.
不过我会失去我的家人
I'm about to lose my... my family here
如果你不告诉我原因的话
If you don't tell me how.
卡西迪奥  求求你告诉我
Please, Castiel, just talk to me.
你究竟要我干什么
What do you want from me?
我懂了
Yes, I understand.
你保证我家人平安无事  我就照做
Promise my family will be okay, and I'll do it.
好吧
Then...yes.
爸爸
Daddy?
我不是你爸爸
I am not your father.
我们
We, uh...
我们没继续找你
We stopped looking for you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你死了
You were dead.
我们认为你已经死了
We, uh, we thought you were dead.
我没事
I'm okay.
克莱尔  快回房间
Claire, room, now.
我能看看她吗
Can I see her?
不行
Oh...no.
我还不确定
I don't know yet.
差不多有一年了  你知道吗
It's been almost a year, you know?
我知道
I know.
女儿很想知道你是不是平安无事
Think your daughter would have wanted to know you were okay.
我在一家精神病院
I was in a psych clinic.
我要在见你之前调整好
I just wanted to get myself straight before seeing you.
没个电话什么的
And no telephones, or...?
我知道  你说的对
No. I know. You're right. I'm...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不过一切都过去了
But it's all, it's all over now.
我现在没事了
I mean, I'm... I'm really okay.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
艾米莉娅  我一时糊涂
I...I was, I was confused, Amelia.
我得了妄想症
I was completely delusional.
我以为上帝吩咐我做事
And I thought, I thought god was calling me to something,
我以为是很重要的事
And I thought that it was important.
不过
And...
我错了
I was wrong.
我是个大笨蛋
I was such an idiot.
天堂  地狱
Heaven, hell...
根本没有那些东西
None of that matters.
对我来说  你和克莱尔才是最重要的
The only thing that's important to me is you and Claire.
虽然我
And I, uh...
无法挽回我犯下的错
I can't undo what I've done.
不过我希望一家团聚
But I just want to come home again.
我不知道自己能不能接受
I don't know if I can do that.
现在还不行
Not yet.
你看着办吧
I mean, whatever you're comfortable with.
也许我们可以从些小事开始
Maybe we could start with something smaller?
比如呢
Like what?
我不知道
I don't know.
晚餐
Dinner?
你他娘的到底去哪儿呢  露比
where the hell are you, Ruby?
这可不是开玩笑的
This isn't funny anymore.
我喝完了
I'm all out.
不管你在干吗
Stop whatever you're doing.
马上打给我
Call me.
我还要更多的血
I need more.
爸爸
Hi, daddy.
亲爱的
Hi, baby.
我们今天吃火鸡加烤肉三明治
Okay, so, we have turkey and roast beef.
家里就剩这些了
Better be okay. it's all we have.
不错
It's fine.
太好了
It's more than fine.
大家坐下吧
Shall we sit?
恩
Yeah.
太完美了
It's perfect.
爸  你不做感恩祷告么
Daddy... aren't you gonna say grace?
不亲爱的  我想我不会再做了
no, honey, I don't think I am.
你为什么哭了
Why are you crying?
因为太高兴了
'cause I'm happy.
罗杰
Hey, Roger.
艾姆斯  你还好吧
Hey, ames. how you doing?
还好
Good.
半小时前我看到你老公在周围晃悠
Am I crazy, or did I just see
我是不是看错了
Your husband wander in here about half an hour ago?
没错  就是他
Yeah, uh, you did.
罗杰  现在不是很方便
But, Roger, now's not a good time --
嘿  真是他
Hey. there he is.
该死的混蛋  你跑哪里去了
Son of a bitch. what the hell happened to you?
说来话长
Uh...long story.
不过这一切都结束了
But it's over.
是么
Yeah?
我很好
I'm good.
我能跟你说几句话么
Can I talk to you?
喝啤酒么
Can I get you a beer?
太好了
That'd be good.
谢谢
Thanks.
死过来
get in here.
哥们儿  你可真是吓死大家了
Buddy, you scared the hell out of a lot of people.
我知道
I know, I know.
说真的  到底怎么回事
So, really, what happened?
说真的么
Honestly?
人生低谷啊
Worst year of my life,
你绝对不会相信的
And you wouldn't believe a word of it.
不过一切都结束了
But... it's all okay now.
我发誓
Swear.
事实上  还没有结束
Actually, no, it's not.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我会当着你的面将你女儿开膛破肚
Well, I mean, I'm gonna gut your daughter while you watch.
给
Here you go.
你在干么什么
What are you doing?!
-他是个恶魔  -吉米  停下来
- He's a demon! - Jimmy, stop!
-快跑  -停下来
- Run! run! - stop it!
-盐在哪里  --罗杰是你朋友
- Where is it? - Roger was your best friend.
罗杰是个恶魔
Roger was a demon.
别跨过这条线
Don't cross this line.
吉米  还说你好多了  其实是病的很严重了
Jimmy, you thought you were better. but you are so sick.
-听着  我没疯  -离我们远点
- Look, I'm not crazy. - stay the hell away from us!
-离我们远点  -我是说真的
- Just stay the hell away from us! - this is very, very real.
克莱尔  快跑
Claire! no! run!
别去纠缠她
Leave her alone!
呆在这里
Please stay there!
克莱尔
Claire!
见鬼
Damn it!
嘿  兄弟
Hey, pal.
-我说过会将她开膛破肚的  -罗杰
- Told you I'd gut the bitch.  - Roger.
-爸  - 放她走好么
- Daddy? - just let her go, okay?
我可能会哟
Now, me -- I would.
不过那位夫人可能有别的想法
But the missus -- she has other ideas.
爸
Daddy!
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
不
No!
快  带他们离开
go! get them out of here!
快
Go! go!
看样子你坚持不住啊  萨姆
Can't get it up, can you, Sam?
不过我可以
No, but I can.
快  快跟上  走走
Come on, come on, come on.
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
-你妻子呢  -这里
- Where's your wife? - right here.
快走
Let's go!
你说的没错
You were right.
我们当然没错
Sorry we were.
不过说实话  我真的什么都不记得了
But I'm telling you -- I don't know anything.
我可不觉得他们会相信你
I don't think they're inclined to believe you.
即便他们相信你  但你是个天使载体
And even if they did, you're a vessel.
他们还是会想知道这是怎么个原理
They're still gonna want to know what makes you tick.
也就是说活体解剖  假如他们心情好的话
Which means vivisection... if they're feeling generous.
我再告诉你一遍
I'm gonna tell you once again --
你让你的家人陷入了危险
You're putting your family in danger.
你必须跟我们一起走
You have to come with us.
多久呢
How long?
别跟我扯什么不会很久的狗屁
And don't give me that "cross that bridge when we get to it" crap.
你还是不了解
Don't you get it?
是永远
Forever.
恶魔会永远跟着你
The demons will never stop.
你决不能和你的家人在一起
You can never be with your family.
你要么离她们远远的
So, you either get as far away from them as possible
要么就自杀
Or you put a bullet in your head,
只有这样你才能确保她们的安全
And that's how you keep your family safe,
别再想什么脱身啊  回家啊的
But there's no getting out and there's no going home.
你说的还真直接啊  萨姆
Well, don't sugarcoat it, Sam.
我只是实话实说罢了  迪恩
I'm just telling him the truth, Dean.
必须有人告诉他
Someone has to.
看样子  我之前真是大错特错了
So...I pretty much owe you the biggest apology ever.
不  你没错
No, you don't.
我当然错了
Yes. I do.
我很抱歉  吉米
I'm so sorry, Jimmy.
我永远不会原谅我自己的
And I will never, ever forgive myself
竟然让你就这样走了
For letting you walk out that door.
正常人都会那么做的
Well, you did what any rational person would have done.
我当时也觉得自己有点疯了
I mean, hell, I thought I was crazy half the time.
是恶魔么
So...demons, huh?
没错
Yeah.
我们可不可以
Can we...
我们还能不能回家
Can we even go home, or...?
我们应该怎么做
What are we gonna do?
他们两个会帮你找辆车
These boys are gonna get you a car.
别问我怎么找
Don't ask me how.
你只管带克莱尔去卡尔和莎莉那里
And you're gonna take Claire to Carl and Sally's
越快越好
As fast as you can.
那你呢
Wait. what about you?
没有你我哪里都不去
No. I-I'm not going anywhere without you, Jimmy.
听着
Listen to me.
跟我在一起的每分每秒
Every moment that I'm with you,
你和克莱尔都在危险中
You and Claire are in danger.
我不管  我们不会再分开了
I don't care. we are not splitting up again.
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
那多久呢
For how long?
用不了多久的
We'll...cross that bridge when we get to it.
我们可是一家人
we're family.
它们会杀了你的  艾米莉娅
They will kill you, Amelia.
还有克莱尔
And they'll kill Claire.
你必须离我越远越好
You just have to get as far away from me as you can.
给  这是你的车
Okay, so, uh... here's your car.
好好照顾你妈妈  听到没  宝贝
Take care of your mom, okay, bub?
为什么他又要走
Why is he leaving again?
今天怎么这么不顺
This is just not my day, is it?
你这个小贱人
You little bitch.
刚刚怎么回事啊你
What the hell happened back there?
怎么了
What?
你几乎无力杀死恶魔
You practically fainted trying to gank a demon.
好吧  我没变弱
Okay, I didn't faint.
只是有点晕眩
I got a little dizzy.
随你怎么说
Well, you can call it whatever you want.
关键是  之前杀阿拉斯泰尔你都易如反掌
Point is, you used to be strong enough to kill alastair.
而如今却连一个蹩脚恶魔都搞不定
Now you can't even kill stunt demon number three?
你想让我说什么  迪恩
What do you want me to say about it, Dean?
首先  你的魔力怎么回事
For starters, what's going on with your mojo?
我是说  老是摇摆不定
I mean, it's yo-yo'ing all over the place.
我不是挑衅  好吗
Now, I'm not trying to pick a fight here, okay?
只是  你吓到我了  兄弟
I just -- y-you're scaring me, man.
我自己都大吃一惊呢
I'm scaring myself.
喂
Hello?
你是谁
Who is this?
你老婆
It's your wife.
艾米莉娅
Amelia?
天啊
Oh, my god.
好吧  他们盼着你独自归来呢
All right, they're expecting you to come alone.
而你则顺着他们的意
That's exactly what you're gonna do.
我们自有办法一展拳脚
We'll work our way through the catwalks.
我们会保护你
We'll be right behind you.
你只要保持冷静  拖延时间  让我们做足准备
All you got to do is stay calm and stall and let us do our job.
你们想要我保持冷静
You want me to stay calm?
我们谈论的可是我家人
This is my family we're talking about.
听我说  会起效的
Listen to me -- this will work.
明白吗  没人会受伤
You understand? nobody's gonna get hurt.
不管了
Whatever.
给我一分钟  好吗
Give me a minute, okay?
恶魔们不可能会想着他独自回来的  迪恩
There's no way they're expecting him to come alone, Dean.
这可能是个陷阱
You know this is probably a trap.
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
所以我才打了如意算盘
That's why I have a plan.
卡西迪奥  你这个混蛋
Castiel, you son of a bitch!
你答应过我  我家人会没事
You promised me my family would be okay!
你答应过我  会好好照顾她们
You promised you were gonna take care of them!
你要我做的我都做了
I've gave you everything you asked me to give!
甚至更多
I gave you more!
这就是我的回报
This is the thanks I get?
这就是你的作为
This is what you do?
这就是你所谓的天堂
Your heaven?!
请帮帮我
Help me, please!
你答应过的  卡西
You promised, Cass!
帮帮我
Just help me!
真有你的
Typical.
亲爱的  你回来啦
Hi, honey. you're home.
听着  我
Listen, I'm...
我求求你
I'm begging you here.
随便你怎么对我
You d-do whatever you want with me...
但我老婆和孩子  她们只是
But my wife and daughter, they're just --
她们是无辜的
They're not a part of this.
她们可是相当重要的  吉米
Oh, they're a big part of this, Jimmy.
补充说一句  你该独自回来
And p.s. -- you should have come alone.
就我一个
I am alone.
你撒谎
Oh, you're such a liar.
我想你带着并非海克尔和杰克尔(动画片主角)
Like I didn't think you'd bring heckle and jeckle.
见鬼
Damn it.
计划不错  迪恩
Nice plan, Dean.
是啊  没人能洞晓一切
Yeah, well, nobody bats a thousand.
拿到刀了吗
Got the knife?
知道啥才叫好玩吗
And you know what's funny?
做起中年妇女啦
You wearing a soccer mom?
实际上我并不乐意说细节
Is I was actually bummed to get this detail.
拿个空盆来
Picking up an empty vessel?
那啥像牛奶般倾泻而出
Sort of like a milk run.
现在来看看是谁倒在我怀里
Now look who landed in my lap.
是的  好吧
Yeah, well...
你抓了我们  好吗
You got us, okay?
放这些人走
Let these people go.
萨姆
Oh, Sam.
当你的美男计不起作用时
It's easy to act chivalrous
侠义之心又开始作怪啦
When your wonder girl powers aren't working, huh?
可笑的是
Now for the punch line --
没人能活着离开
Everybody dies.
杀了小孤儿安妮
Waste little orphan annie.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
我们当然会恪守承诺
Of course we keep our promises.
也当然懂得知恩图报
Of course you have our gratitude.
你效力的不错
You served us well.
你的任务完成了
Your work is done.
现在是时候回家了  你真正的家
It's time to go home now -- your real home.
你将在天堂里欢度余生
You'll rest forever in the fields of the lord.
不要
No.
安息吧  吉米
Rest now, Jimmy.
不  别是克莱尔
No. Claire.
她现在和我在一起
She's with me now.
这是她的命运
She's chosen.
她命中注定  你也一样
It's in her blood, as it was in yours.
求你了  卡西迪奥
please, Castiel.
附我的身
I mean, just -- just take me.
附我的身  求求你
Take me, please.
我得确保你理解
I want to make sure you understand.
你不会死  也不会老
You won't die... or age.
如果这一年让你伤心欲绝
If this last year was painful for you,
那么这一年将会轮回一百  一千次
Picture a hundred -- a thousand more like it.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
附我的身
You take me.
附我身吧
Just take me.
如你所愿
As you wish.
卡西  等等
Cass, hold up.
你想告诉我什么
What were you gonna tell me?
在离开这段时间我搞懂了一件事儿  迪恩
I learned my lesson while I was away, Dean.
我为天堂服务  而不是人类
I serve heaven. I don't serve man.
当然也不服务于你
And I certainly don't serve you.
好吧
All right.
说出来吧
Let's hear it.
怎么了
What?
别憋着  伙计
Drop the bomb, man.
你看见我的所作所为了  来吧  停车  狠狠揍我吧
You saw what I did. come on. stop the car. take a swing.
我不会打揍你的
I'm not gonna take a swing.
那么大吼大叫吧  狠狠骂我
Then scream. chew me out.
我不生气  萨姆
I'm not mad, Sam.
得了吧  你没生气吗
Oh, come on. you're not mad?
没有
No.
好吧  至少让我解释下
Right. look, at least let me explain myself.
别解释
Don't.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你不在乎
You don't care?
你想我说什么  我很失望吗
What do you want me to say -- that I'm disappointed?
是的  我失望透了
Yeah, I am.
但主要  我累了  伙计
But mostly, I'm just tired, man.
我受够了
And I'm done.
我只是受够了
I am just done.
喂  鲍比
Hey, Bobby.
喂  你和你哥哥最好赶快来我这儿
Hey, you and your brother better shag ass to my place asap.
怎么了
What's going on?
是天启  先知  现在就来
The apocalypse, genius. now, get your asses over here.
他说了什么
What'd he say?
谢谢你的热烈欢迎
Well, thanks for shaking a tail.
很高兴你们来
Glad you got here.
现在进去  给你们看样东西
Now, go on inside. I want to show you something.
好吧
All right.
问题症结出在哪
So, uh, what's the big demon problem?
是你
You are.
这是为了你好
This is for your own good.
伙计
Guys?
Hey. guys!
这不好玩
This isn't funny!
伙计
Guys!
喂
Hey!
伙计们
Guys!